# Corey Paskewitz

SOFTWAREENGINEER

corey.paskewitz@gmail.com 647-390-8870 linkedin.com/in/corey-paskewitz github.com/cpaskewitz cpaskewitz.com

#### **PROFILE**

Starting with Unity game development, I discovered the magic of coding-transforming abstract ideas into interactive experiences. This initial curiosity grew into a dedicated pursuit of software engineering at BrainStation, where I deepened my understanding of technology's power to solve complex problems. Today, I bring together my story-telling skills from Unity and the comprehensive coding expertise acquired, ready to contribute to innovative projects that tell their own unique stories.

#### **SKILLS**

HTML, CSS, JavaScript, Node, React, Express, MySQL, MongoDB, Typescript, Next.js, React Native, Redux, Agile Development, Document Object Model (DOM) APIs, Web APIs, User Authentication, OAuth, Heroku, GitHub, Visual Studio, Tailwind, Unit Testing, Jest, C#, C++, PHP, Unity, Jira, Microsoft Suite, Lenel, Sharepoint, iCIMS

#### **Certificates**

Unity Game Developer, Unreal Engine Developer, Unity Mobile Developer, Unity Multiplayer: Intermediate, Complete Web Developer Course 2.0

#### **PROJECTS**

## Software Engineer | BoguStore

SEP 2024, BoguStore

 Developed a mock e-commerce store using Next.js, Tailwind, and Redux, showcasing unit testing using Jest.

## Software Engineer | QuestListRPG

JUNE 2024, QuestListRPG

 Developed and deployed a task manager app with game elements using MERN stack, Dalle3 API and Typescript via Heroku.

## Software Engineer | PetAdoptr

APR 2024, BRAINSTATION, CAPSTONE

• Created a mobile app for users to easily find animals near them available for adoption, using React, Express, Node and MySQL.

#### **EXPERIENCE**

## Wordpress Developer | Self-employed

MAY 2021 - PRESENT, PUSLINCH, ON

- Developed a customized swim lesson booking website servicing over 500 users monthly, utilizing PHP, advanced plugins, and Google API for map and reviews functionalities.
- Administered web hosting and maintained plugins and databases for a medium-traffic swim lesson site on WordPress, managed through GoDaddy, supporting over 1,000 monthly unique visits.
- Managed and optimized a dynamic booking calendar tailored to meet the scheduling needs of 200+ clients per month, ensuring seamless booking experiences and high client satisfaction.

# Human Resource Coordinator & Scheduler | Allied Universal

JUN 2023 - JAN 2024, WATERLOO, ON

- Proactively managed internal inquiries for over 400 employees, ensuring clarity and compliance in HR policies, payroll and benefits, resulting in a 15% decrease in HR-related issues.
- Delivered a client satisfaction score of 97%, managing a workforce of over 400 employees across 15+ clients.
- Monitored and recorded sick and vacation days for Waterloo, London and Windsor region, resulting in a 15% decrease in absences.

#### Senior Supervisor Team Lead | Allied Universal

JAN 2020 - JUN 2023, WATERLOO, ON

- Guided a diverse 5-member team, driving the successful implementation of industry standard security solutions.
- Facilitated, managed and audited multiple technical platforms, demonstrating high proficiency in various software applications and contributing to a 35% improvement in operational efficiency.

## **EDUCATION**

### **BrainStation** | Diploma, Software Engineering

APR 2024, TORONTO, ON